celebgeek.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy – CelebGeek

This Privacy Policy explains how MediaGleam (d/b/a CelebGeek, “CelebGeek” or “we”) collects, protects, uses and shares information about you when you use the CelebGeek website (the “Site”). We hope this information increases your confidence in CelebGeek and enhances your experience on our Site. Each time that you use the Site, you signify that you agree to be bound by the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy you must discontinue using the Service and terminate your membership if you are a registered user.

  1. **ABOUT  CELEBGEEK**

CelebGeek.com is an online site providing rich content surrounding the celebrity and entertainment verticals.

  1. **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Like most standard Website servers, we collect information from all visitors to the Site. We collect this information using a variety of methods, including weblogs, cookies, web beacons, widgets and the like.

Cookies we utilize on the Site may include session ID cookies, persistent cookies, or more advanced technology such as HTML5 or Media Stamp. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. You may configure your browser to prevent cookies from being set on your computer. If you reject cookies you may still use the Site but your ability to use some areas of the Site may be limited and you may not be able to use certain features of the Site, including playing games or entering sweepstakes or contests.

Similar cookies and other technologies are used by our partners, which may also include Flash cookies, which are a form of persistent cookies technically called “Local Shared Objects” (LSOs). Flash cookies are set through a mechanism in Adobe Flash Player. With Flash cookies your data is stored in multiple places and it may be restored once you delete it. Please check with your browser’s site on the most updated information on how to delete Flash cookies. HTML5 or Media Stamp technology has a local storage feature that, when used, allows for quicker access to a website upon a return visit. HTML5 is currently supported by some mobile devices and desktop browsers. HTML5 Media Stamp data is not stored in a browser’s “cookies” file.

Our Site web pages and our e-mail newsletters contain web beacons (also known as pixel tags). These web beacons allow us and our partners to count users who have visited a web page or opened a newsletter, as well as to collect the other types of information described below.

The information we collect through the Site includes, but is not limited to, the browser you are using, the internet address from which you linked to our Site, the operating system of your computer, the unique IP address of the computer you used to access our Site, and usage and browsing habits on the Site. We and our partners also use cookies, pixels and these other technologies to collect data regarding your browsing, engagement and purchasing habits on our Site and on other internet websites.

In addition to the foregoing, the Site provides search functionality and we collect the searches conducted on the Site by a user and may combine that information with other information from such user.

**III. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the information we collect that is associated with a single user or Member, or combined in the aggregate is known as “Data.” We keep Data no longer than necessary for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

**General Use of Site.** We use the Data we collect, including both personally identifiable information (“PII”) and non-PII in both aggregated and individual forms, to provide the Site, advertising and Site support. We may process and use this Data for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy including, but not limited to:

  * Customize, measure, and improve the Site design and optimization, and the content and advertising provided through it, which include research and development;
  * Enforce our Terms of Service and detect fraud and other illegal activities;
  * Let you know about new products or services from us or other companies we work with as well as promotional offers, based on your preference settings;
  * Evaluate potential inclusion in the Site’s influencer program;
  * Let you know about changes to the Site, the Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, and other terms that apply to our Site; and
  * Update any programs or other tools that we provide in conjunction with the Site.

In addition we may combine the Data we have collected with similar types of data provided by third parties for similar purposes. We use this Data to create a better Site and better user experience, as well as to help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, to analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We may use this Data in these forms for internal business purposes, such as determining how much traffic certain portions of the Site receive, for license reporting and assessment of service levels, to better understand how the Site is used, to gauge traffic patterns and determine what types of content and services are most popular with users of the Site, or determining which search queries are the most popular.

Using this Data, we are able to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Site. This allows us to learn what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which parts of our Site are the most interesting and what kind of offers our Members like to see.

We use cookies to differentiate users of the Site from Members, to customize the content of certain sections of the Site and to enable us to track and cater to the interests of users, in order to enhance their experience on the Site. For example, we may use such Data to determine which blogs, articles, or games to recommend to you. We may also use Data to send you targeted offers and other communications.

We may use a Member’s registration information to verify that you are the person authorized to use the Site or to manage your account.

**Advertisements.** We, or our partners acting at our request, may deliver advertisements to you through the Site or through third party sites, as described in more detail below.

Contextual Advertising

We, or our advertising partners, automatically deliver ads to all users of the Site, whether they are registered or not, based on non-personal information including: (i) the IP address associated with your computer or location data from your mobile phone for purposes of determining your approximate geographic location; (ii) the type of web page that is being displayed, such as a news or games page, for example; (iii) the content on the page that is shown, such as a news article about a certain movie; (iv) the browser you are using; (v) the operating system and/or computer brand you are using; and (vi) for mobile users, the cellular network you are using. This advertising activity automatically applies to all users and it is purely contextual.

  1. **IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

CelebGeek contains links to other sites. It is possible for you to receive information directly from our partners and other companies if you access them through a link on the Site or if you go directly to their Websites. Once you are on their sites, any data that you supply to these partners, for example, to obtain information or buy products directly from them, is beyond our reach and will be the responsibility of each of the linked-to entities and not CelebGeek. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Websites or any other sites linked to or referenced on our Site.

**Security.** We have multiple layers of security on our systems. We have implemented software and hardware security, including firewalls, data encryption, and private networks intended to protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access. We use firewalls and intrusion-detection devices that are designed to defend against hackers and notify us if any attempts are made to compromise our network. We regularly review additional software upgrades to enhance our security measures. However, despite our efforts, no system can completely guaranty that there will never be unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information, and your use of the Site indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.

**Your California Privacy Rights.** Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the address referenced below.

**A Note to Users Based Outside of the United States.** Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your PII will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may be different than other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create an online account to use the Site as a visitor from outside the United States, you will have agreed to the terms of the Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service and you will have consented to the transfer to and processing of all such information in the United States, which many not offer an equivalent level of protection of that in the European Union or certain other countries.

**Children’s Privacy.**  CelebGeek does not encourage participation or visitation by children. Visitors who are known to be under the age of 16 are prohibited from becoming CelebGeek Members. CelebGeek does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16.

**Updating Your Personal Information.** If you are a CelebGeek Member, you can update your personally identifiable information at any time. To do this, just click on the “Privacy + Settings” link listed throughout the Site. However, we are unable to update or delete any of your personally identifiable information that has been shared with a third party as permitted in this Privacy Policy.

**Waiver.**  CELEBGEEK ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY WITH REGARD TO ANY THEFT, LOSS, ALTERATION OR MISUSE OF PERSONAL OR OTHER INFORMATION LAWFULLY PROVIDED BY CELEBGEEK TO THIRD PARTIES, OR WITH REGARD TO THE FAILURE OF ANY THIRD PARTY TO ABIDE BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR AGREEMENT BETWEEN THAT THIRD PARTY AND CELEBGEEK.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, or we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information. By using our Site or services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

**Contacting Us.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of this Site, please contact us at mediagleam@gmail.com
